<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shivam Behl</title>
    <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shivam Behl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 02:41:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shivambehl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flipkart</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/experience/flipkart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/experience/flipkart/</guid>
      <description>Since January 2021, I have been working at Flipkart, Jan 2021 to June 2021 as a Intern and since July of same year as a full time Software Development Engineer.
Team Here at Flipkart, I am part of Jeeves team which works to imporve experiece of customers and technicians for various post delivery services provided by Fk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/thapar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/thapar/</guid>
      <description>This is my graduation school, I majored in Computer Engineering here.
Academics Here are few subjects which I took and enjoyed in here, go ahead if this peeks your interest: (Just sharing my favourites here)
Semester Eight  UCS742 - INTERNSHIP  Semester Seven  UCS742 - DEEP LEARNING UCS794 - CAPSTONE - Worked with an Amazing team and delivered NARAD: more about it in projects!  Semester Six  UCS633 - DATA ANALYTICS &amp;amp; VISUALIZATION UCS525 - PROFESSIONAL PRACTICES UTA012 - INNOVATION AND ENTREPRENEURSHIP UML602 - NATURAL LANGUAGE PROCESSING  Semester Five  UHU008 - INTRODUCTION TO CORPORATE FINANCE UML501 - MACHINE LEARNING UCS615 - IMAGE PROCESSING  Semester Four  UTA014 - ENGINEERING DESIGN PROJECT - II: The Buggy Project UCS409 - PROBABILITY AND STATISTICS UCS406 - DATA STRUCTURES AND ALGORITHMS  Semester Three  UTA013 - ENGINEERING DESIGN PROJECT - I: The Mangonal Project UCS405 - DISCRETE MATHEMATICAL STRUCTURES UCS303 - OPERATING SYSTEMS UCS520 - COMPUTER NETWORKS  Semester Two  UTA018 - OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING UTA015 - ENGINEERING DRAWING UHU003 - PROFESSIONAL COMMUNICATION UMA004 - MATHEMATICS - II  Semester One  UTA017 - COMPUTER PROGRAMMING - I UCB008 - APPLIED CHEMISTRY UMA003 - MATHEMATICS - I UES009 - MECHANICS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKSD Public School, Kaithal</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/rksdschool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/rksdschool/</guid>
      <description>From class 9th to 12th, I studied at RKSD Public School, in Kaithal Haryana and graduated in 2017.s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maharishi Vidya Mandir</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/mvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/education/mvm/</guid>
      <description>This was my first school and the only school I attended in my home town - Yamuna Nagar.
I attended MVM from Pre Nursery to class 8th.
Fun Fact 1: Before begining of school activities and before leaving for home, we used to meditation in school. School policy, cool huh?! :)
Fun Fact 2: I was part of National Cadit Corps and have NCC &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; Certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo Attentive Relief Architecture for Disaster</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/narad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/narad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Intelligence System</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/fashioninteligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/fashioninteligence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TopsisPy</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/topsispy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/about/projects/topsispy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder for something cool, lol</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/cool/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/cool/placeholder/</guid>
      <description>Hey, this is a placeholder for something cool :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Post</title>
      <link>https://shivambehl.github.io/posts/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shivambehl.github.io/posts/placeholder/</guid>
      <description>Hey, this is a placeholder Post, Will add posts soon :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
